Dragon's Claws is a action film directed by Joseph Kuo.
A "Dragon Claw" master returns from Manchuria
where he became a traitor to China.
He's after the coveted Dragon Claw Golden Tablet that
will force people to bow down to him.
He challenges the Grand-master who has a checkered past of his own.
The Grand-master happens to suffers from a terminal
chronic injury related to his evil past.
The traitor kills the grand-master, causing his wife and son the go into hiding.
The wife seems to really be the Dragon Claw master in the family
and she vows to train her son the kung fu secrets.
The son finds that one of his friends has learned a strange
style of kung fu from a filthy medicine man.
The son seeks him out to improve his kung fu and defeat the traitor.
Lung Hsia, played by Lau Ga-Yung.
Ling Ko Fung, played by Hwang Jang-Lee.
Beggar Medicine man, played by Pak Sha-Lik.
A Tsai, played by Hon Kwok-Choi.
Red Monster, played by Chu Tit-Wo.
Green Monster, played by Chan Lau.
Dragon's Claws is a British dystopian science fiction comic book,
published by Marvel UK about the eponymous law enforcers.
Dragon's Claws first appeared in Dragon's Claws #1 (June 1988),
and were created by Simon Furman and Geoff Senior.
Before their career as law enforcers, the Claws had been "the greatest Game players in the world" - the Game was a violent team sport, immensely
popular and funded by the governing  World Development Council, who had used it to distract the population and reduce civil unrest.
Many of the villains appearing in the series also have their roots in the Game.